http://thepregnancycentre.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
The Pregnancy Centre respects its users privacy. The Pregnancy Centre upholds a strict privacy policy which protects personal information obtained through the website.
Personal Information
You can visit the The Pregnancy Centre Site without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. Our web servers collect the domain names, not the e-mail addresses, of visitors.
In general, we gather information about users of the Site collectively in order to determine statistics such as the popularity of certain sections of the site. This sort of information helps us to continually improve our site and provide a better experience for the users.
Cookies
There is a technology called "cookies" which is an element of data in the form of a small text file that a Web site can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your system.
Some Site pages use cookies so that we can better serve you when you return to our Site. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving the chance to decide whether to accept it.
Web Site Links
The Pregnancy Centre’s Site may contain links to other Web sites such as The Pregnancy Centre distributors and sales representatives.
While The Pregnancy Centre tries to link only to sites that share its high standards and respect for privacy, The Pregnancy Centre cannot take responsibility for the content or the privacy practices employed by other sites.
Changes
If at anytime The Pregnancy Centre changes its privacy policy, those changes will be displayed here so that you will know what information The Pregnancy Centre gathers and how that information might be used.
